Guide to the Linda Mary Montano Papers MSS.386
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series II: Inspirational People and Collaborators
  - Love Art Laboratory: Annie Sprinkle Wedding Invitations [2 of 2], 2003-2010 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Dr. Mehta: Chakra Posters, undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Dr. Mehta: "The Collected Words and Advice of Dr. Aruna Mehta", 1990-2000 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Mitchell Payne and Ken Graves: "American Snapshots" Poster, undated (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Mitchell Payne Oversize Self-Portrait Photography, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Mitchell Payne Photographs, undated (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Pauline Oliveros: Sonic Meditations, March-November 1971 (Box 81)
  - Linda Montano and Tehching Hsieh Art Life: One Year Performance, 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Tehching Hsieh: One Year Performances Promotional Material, 1980-1999 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Tehching Hsieh: One Year Performance Silkscreen Print, undated (Folder 7)
- OVERSIZE Series III: Correspondence
  - Letter to Linda with Melon Seed Rosary, undated (Box 81)
  - Oversize Correspondence, 1987, 1999, 2012 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Teaching
  - Student Work: Promotional Posters, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Family and Juvenilia
  - Dad Art Diploma, 1931, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Dad Art: Henry Montano X-Rays, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Dad Art: Oversize Graduation Photo, 1927 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Henry J. Montano St. Mary's Diploma, June 26, 1927 (Box 81)
  - High School Reunion Photos, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Lena Becker Kelly Scrapbook (Box 84)
    from Linda Montano: "My grandmother Lena Kelly Lena Becker Kelly made this. Died mid-'60s. I went to her house every day and watched her work (art) in silence. She was my mentor. I looked at this book of hers often."
  - Mildred Kelly Diploma, undated (Box 81)
  - Mildred M. Montano Yearbook Photo, 1933 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Montano Family Photograph Album, undated (Box 84)
  - Montano Family Photos, undated (Box 75, Folder 13)